so I wrote this song about a girl
you
- rebar beams and Shiva cladding and
knee-high skirt and dress socks there
sits college graduate with a degree in
women's studies she stands on the
shoulders of giants when she rides
subways in elevators built by
Minaj's of people who understand nature
another night you won't remember with
some folks that are so forgettable
so go study hands vigorously
agree over fair trade coffee you
economic pervert
and man free birth control while you're
pregnant with liberal gills
I will leave the water running when I
brush my teeth just to piss you off will
drain the reservoirs and laugh at your
sad excuse for an education I haven't
gone gone yet but you make me wanna sit
and watch the world burn
[Music]
you
so gather up your pretenses if you
believe that truth is privilege round up
your friends and build an airplane out
of pixie dust and empowerment and fly
yourselves to postmodern paradise
[Music]
I want to drop out I want to drop out I
want to drop out
hi I want to drop out
[Music]